Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Speak! Who are you?
I am from the ocean.
Who are you in the ocean?
I am the spirit of lust.
Yes.
What have you done to her?
She always runs to God.
You do not want her to run to God?
No.
Why?
I hate God.
You hate God.
Yes.
Who are you, if you hate God? Who are you?
I am the spirit of lust.
Spirit of lust?
Yes.
From which kingdom are you?
Light or darkness?
Darkness.
Yes.
As a spirit of lust, what have you done to her marriage?
She will not have an affection for her husband.
She will not have an affection for her husband?
No.
What has that caused between her and her husband?
They used to fight.
Who caused this fight?
Me.
You caused the fight?
Yes.
How long have you been living in this body?
Since she was small, from eight years.
Eight years?
Yes.
How did you enter her?
I sent a boy.
You sent a boy?
Yes.
What did the boy do to her?
He initiated her.
He initiated her?
Yes.
Who is this?
It’s her daughter.
Is she not your daughter?
No.
Who is she to you?
I make her frustrated.
You frustrate her?
How do you do it?
Disobedience.
I make her feel that she is not listening to her mother.
Why do you do that to her as little as she is?
I wanted to make her hate her mother.
To make her hate her mother?
Yes.
Were you able to achieve that?
No.
Why was it difficult for you to achieve that?
It is because of this ministry.
Because of this ministry?
Yes.
What is wrong with this ministry that you don't like?
It sets people free.
It sets people free?
Yes, from darkness.
What is your trouble with that? Is it not a good thing to set people free from darkness?
No, we hate people.
You hate people being set free from darkness?
Yes.
That means that you belong to the kingdom of darkness?
How are you?
I am fine.
Who is she to you?
My mummy.
She said that you are her mom.
No.
I am not her mum.
OK, tell her.
You are my mummy.
No, I have nothing to do with her.
Are you sure she is your mum?
Yes.
Right now, it's time to leave this body.
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus, you demon!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come out of her, you spirit of lust!
Out, n the mighty name of Jesus!
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Out!
Out, in the mighty name of Jesus!
In Jesus' name.
Thank You, Lord.
You are delivered.
Rise up.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you?
I am fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Who is this?
This is my daughter.
Are you sure this is your daughter?
Yes.
Earlier you said that you do not know her.
I gave birth to her.
You gave birth to her?
Yes.
But you denied her just now.
No. I will never deny her.
You will never deny her and this is your daughter?
Yes.
You said you were the spirit of lust living inside her.
No, I cannot be a spirit.
So that very demon that was tormenting you is out. You are free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Are you happy now that your mum says that you are her daughter?
Yes.
Are you happy?
Give her a hug.
Thank you.
Thank you Jesus!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Indeed, God is with us.
My name is Carolien Coetzee, I am 39 years old, I am from Cape Town, South Africa.
The man standing next to me is my husband Emil Coetzee.
The reason we came to The SCOAN in Lagos is to share our wonderful testimony
of what God has done for us in our lives.
If it was not for this ministry, the living church we have seen,
we would not be here today to say "Jesus is Lord".
I received my deliverance from the spirit of abuse, which was constantly tormenting me for almost 29 years.
I heard constant voices in my head, which I all this years thought were me.
I always felt rejected, not good enough, always striving, being busy, never being able to settle down.
While doing things at home like cooking, I would be worrying about tomorrow or other things.
I would always be struggling and be frustrated.
Obviously, the atmosphere in the house was not good.
Even when I looked at other women, I would always feel not beautiful, not good enough,
and I would always try to hide myself.
We then decided to come for the candlelight service in 2012.
I wanted to bring my daughter, just to experience the blessing here.
I thank God because as wise man Daniel laid his hands on me, the spirit manifested -
the spirit of lust who was from the ocean.
I really didn't have any affection for my husband.
We would quarrel and fight constantly, never settling issues, just moving along,
hoping that it would be better tomorrow, or it would be settled by itself.
I just give glory to God that I brought my daughter, because if I hadn't brought her,
God could not have revealed the plan of the enemy to destroy our relationship.
Little did I know that the plan that the enemy had was for her to hate me.
Yes, I can confirm that it was a constant struggle with her in the house.
I would hear that voice telling me that she is disobedient. I felt frustrated with her.
I felt that she was not giving her best.
I can just confirm that since the deliverance we have such a nice relationship.
I just say, "Thank You, Jesus, for what You have done, for using this ministry, for using the wise men,
for using the man of God, to give us an opportunity to come here and receive our deliverance,
so that we can be free Christians, and really walk as born-again".
Can you now explain to us -
how did that affect your relationship with your husband and your daughter?
Well, the relationship with my husband - I had no affection for my husband.
If he wanted to meet as husband and wife, I would constantly look for an excuse.
I didn't have that affection.
And I knew it was not normal but it was like I could not help myself.
It is just the spirit controlling you.
You know it is not normal but you still feel it yourself.
With my daughter - you could see that she was still little then.
I would put out a set of clothes and then we would fight even over the clothes she must wear.
It was this spirit telling me that she is disobedient, she is not listening to you.
That made me to feel really frustrated with her.
But now after the deliverance, what are the differences that you have seen?
Glory be to Jesus!
It is a totally different relationship I have with my daughter now.
I picked her up from school.
Out of her own, she said, "Mummy, you are the best mummy in the world".
And I know if it was not for that deliverance, it would not have been possible.
We spend time together. We really have a good relationship.
And with my husband - I see him now with affection which he is glad of.
We are really growing stronger and stronger every day, and I just thank the Lord for that.
She said that they wouldn't be standing here together today if not for that deliverance.
Now, we would like to listen to the husband
and find out his own experience and his testimony of the deliverance.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Emil Coetzee. I am from Cape Town, South Africa.
My house used to be a very sensitive place -
a place where I used to stand on a tray of eggs,
a place of quarrel between me and my wife.
We would have quarrels, and in a time we would settle, but it would be a continuous situation.
I even noticed that the relationship between my wife and our daughter...
I actually spoke to her, saying, "You should take care of the way you are treating your daughter
because she might just start drifting apart". So I really noticed that.
Can you now share with us - what are the differences that you've seen
in your marriage and in your family since the deliverance?
We thank God.
After a day of work, I actually look forward to get home
There is peace in my house. The relationships are good.
The relationship between my daughter and my wife is wonderful.
The relationship between us: We are free, we can speak,
we can quarrel and make up, we can discuss things.
It's just the way a marriage should be.
And now after receiving this wonderful miracle
and seeing the change in your marriage and in your family,
what is your advice to those who are facing the same situation that you were facing?
I can honestly say, there are many living churches, but for us - if it wasn't for this ministry,
I do not know where our lives would have been.
So I can just encourage people to get linked up, watch Emmanuel TV, follow the Facebook page,
get the podcasts, try to get to The SCOAN, get to one of the branches, whatever you can do.
Distance is not a barrier.
Exactly - distance is not a barrier for Jesus Christ to touch you.
Can you please give us your advice after receiving your deliverance?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My advice to everyone out there is that you should open your heart to God's Word,
to His Spirit, and to His faith.
God can take you from where you are now to where He wants you to be.
Just be open.
We just advise you after your deliverance that you should draw closer to Jesus Christ,
not draw back in the situation that you face,
and that you should make God's Word the standard for you life,
and for your marriage, and train your child up in the way of the Lord, in Jesus' Name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: Mel Flowers 30/06/2018